Guide to the Mary Beth and Richard Hess Technical Manual Collection M1381
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Miscellaneous manuals, catalogs, schematics, brochures, and bulletins
  - Fujinon TV lens operating for A8.5 x 5.5 FRM-11, A14x9FERM-1PB, A18x8.5 FERM-11, 1.7/9-126, A44x9.5FESM-11M, A44x9.5, A14x9FE, and A18x8.5FE lenses, 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Gardiner communications corporation 5.6 meter antenna installation, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Gardiner communications corporation SR4000 satellite vide receiver operator's handbook (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Gateway 2000 getting started for Microsoft Windows 3.1, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - General instrument IDA-450 and IDA-450-22 internal distribution amplifier instructions; catalog number 30621-001 rev.a (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - GTE 70F2, 778E3, 79F1, 775D1, and 755A operation and installation, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folders 1-2)
  - GTE 78E3, 353A, 758B, 46A3-SC, and 11A operation and installation, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folders 3-4)
  - GTE 756A, 758B, 759A, 54A, 353A, 36A2, 46A3, 11A, 52A, 51F, and 361A operation and installation, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folders 1-2)
  - GTE 9002B, 9004A, 9104A, and 9120A operation and installation, 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - GTE 9004A, 9002B, 9104A, 9120A, 778E3, 79F1, 70F2, 54A, 778B3, 353A, 9004A, 46A3-SC, 54A, 51F, 353A, 36A2, 46A3, 353A, and 759A operation and installation, 1979-1981 (Box 41, Folder 3-5)
  - GTE spacenet VCP-1 voice communication package user, 1990 August (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
  - Harrison alive console technical operator, 1979 May (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Harrison MR-4, AIR-7, PRO-7, and PRO-790 console operator, 1985-1990 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Hewlett Packard HP-85 I/O programming guide, 1981 February (Box 43)
  - Hewlett Packard HP-85 plotter/printer rom manual, 1980 January (Box 43)
  - Hewlett Packard HP-85 mass storage rom, 1980 March (Box 43)
  - Hewlett Packard HP-83/85 assembler rom, 1980 December (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Hewlett Packard HP-82940A gpio installation and theory of operation, 1980 July (Box 43)
  - Hewlett Packard 9100A operating and program (Box 43)
  - Hewlett Packard instrumentation catalogs, 1968-1973 and 1981-1996 (Box 44-49)
  - Hewlett Packard application notes 163-2, 222A, 222-2, 222-3, 222-4, 222-10, 222-11, and 222-12 for signature analysis, 1980-1982 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Hewlett Packard application notes 150, 150-1, 150-2, 150-3, 150-4, 150-7, 150-8, 150-9, 150-10, 150-11, 150-12, 150-13, 150-14, and 192 for spectrum analysis, 1971-1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Hewlett Packard application notes 167-4, 167-5, 167-7, 167-11, 167-12, 167-12a, 167-14, 167-15, 167-16, 167-17, 167-18, 167-19, 201-4, 201-6, 201-10, 233-2, 233-3, 233-4, 233-5, 233-6, 298-1, 298-2, 298-3, and 298-4 for digital and data domain measurements, 1976-1981 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Hewlett Packard application notes 123, 262, 63e, 142, 115, 166, 166-2, 271-1, 156-2, and 156-4 miscellaneous, 1970-1978 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Hewlett Packard application notes 64-1, 64-1, 77-1, 77-3, 77-4, 91, 95-1, 155-1, 155-2, 155-3, 164-2, 164-3, 164-4, 170-1, 170-2, 171-1, 171-2, 187-2, 187-4, 187-5, 187-6, and 294 for rf, microwave, and pll, 1970-1980 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Hewlett Packard application notes 90b, 236-3, 8903a, 3357, and 5970a for miscellaneous, 1978-1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Hewlett Packard instrumentation catalogs, 1997-1999 (Box 51)
  - Hitachi VT-8500A video cassette recorder service manual, 1980 August (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Hitachi SK-90 camera alignment preocedure, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - HWP 121005-002 DME-II digital video processor system information, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Ikegami HK-312 color camera instruction manual volume 1, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Ikegami HK-312 color camera instruction manual volume 2, n.d. (Box 52, Folders 2-3)
  - Ikegami ITC-735 color camera instruction, 1988 June (Box 52, Folders 4)
  - Ikegami PM14-3H picture monitor instruction, n.d. (Box 53, Folders 1)
  - Ikegami PM-970 cctv monitor, n.d. (Box 53, Folders 2)
  - Ikegami TA-79E NTSC triax adaptor instruction, n.d. (Box 53, Folders 3-4)
  - Ikegami TKC-970 color film camera instruction, n.d. (Box 53, Folders 5-6)
  - Image video limited 7105 silence monitor, 1980-1983 (Box 53, Folders 8)
  - Image video limited cp-8 control panel, 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folders 9)
  - Image video limited 6010 routing switcher, 1980 (Box 53, Folders 10)
  - International tapetronics RP series technical, 1975 (Box 53, Folders 7)
  - International telephone and telegraph corporation 36a key telephone system, 1972 December (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - JVC CR-6600u color video cassette recorder instructions and schematics, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Kliegl K96/scr digital dimmer operaton, maintenance, and schematics, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Logitech mouse-2-3 installation and operation, 1988 December (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Kloss videobeam 2000 operating instructions and installation guide (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Kodak videofilm notes, 1971-1977 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Kloss Novabeam 100 video projection monitor brochure and owners, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Logitech pop-up dos users, 1989 August (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Mach one digital systems, inc. mach one editor operating, 1978 November (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Mary Beth and Richard Hess manual partial list, 2003 June
    Biographical / Historical
    Mary Beth and Richard Hess are a married couple based in Canada. Richard has been heavily involved in consulting on audio topics along with extensive work in audio preservation. Mary Beth has worked in real estate and with religious organizations. Since focusing on audio preservation Richard has contributed significantly to the field of sound recordings preservation, especially magnetic media preservation. He has freely shared information through articles along with presenting at organizations ranging from the Audio Engineering Society to the Association of Recorded Sound Collections.
  - McCurdy radio industries AT265 mini-cue amplifier, 1982 June (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - McCurdy radio industries SA14023 extended range audio level meter instructions, 1983 April (Box 55, Folders 6)
  - McCurdy radio industries SS3159c disc reproducer instructions, 1978 April (Box 55, Folders 7)
  - McCurdy radio industries SS8800 audio console, 1985 (Box 55, Folders 8)
  - Microdyne corporation 1000 tv modulator, 1980 July (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - McCurdy coeporation brochure, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Microprobe electronics inc. digisound instruction, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Microprobe electronics inc. X-10 controller, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Modern plastic encyclopedia, 1984-1985 (Box 54)
  - Motorola application notes for 1972 including catalog, 1970-1972 (Box 55, Folders 1-2)
  - Motorola application notes for 1970 including catalog, 1968-1970 (Box 56, Folders 1-3)
  - Motorola application notes, data sheets, and miscellaneous publication for 1977 including catalog, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folders 3-4)
  - Motorola application notes for 1982 including catalog, 1982 February (Box 57, Folders 1-2)
  - National semiconductor corporation hybrid products databook, 1981 (Box 57)
  - NEC FS-19 frame synchronizer instruction; catalog number ho1-533-35-201, 1984 (Box 57, Case 4)
  - Norelco PCP-70B/72 hip pack instruction, n.d. (Box 57, Case 5)
  - Norelco PC-72 plumbicon color television system instruction volume 1, n.d. (Box 58, Case 1)
  - Norelco PC-72 plumbicon color television system instruction, n.d. (Box 58, Case 2)
  - Orion research inc. AMU series preliminary operators, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Pacific recorders and engineering corporation ABX technical manual (Box 58, Case 3-4)
  - Pacific recorders and engineering corporation (Box 59, Case 1-2)
  - Panasonic WJ-5500/WJ-5500A special effects generator service; catalog number avd-7905-507, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Peter W. Dahl custom transformers catalog, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Phillips PM 6662/6669 frequency counter operation 3rd edition and service, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Pioneer F-90 FM/AM digital synthesized tuner operating, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Phillips PM 5109 rc generator instruction 4th edition, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Quantel limited DPE 5000 operating, 1981 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Quantel limited DPE 5000SP operating, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - RCA TR-600A video tape recorder catalog; catalog number ta.3420a, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - RCA TR-600 reel servo modification by Recortec operation and maintenance, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - RCA FH line VHF TV transmitter volume III operating; catalog number IB-8027575, n.d. (Box 60, Folders 1-2)
  - RCA FH line VHF TV transmitter volume IV wire tables; catalog number IB-8027598, n.d. (Box 60, Folders 3-4)
  - RCA TP-55B universal multiplexer system and general information; catalog number IB-32530-3 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - RCA TK-28 NTSC color film camera installation, setup, operation, and schematics with additional PAL setup and operation, 1975 (Box 61, Folders 1-3)
  - RCA TK-47 color camera volume III, 1979 September (Box 63, Folders 1-3)
  - RCA TK-76B NTSC portable television camera installation, operation, setup, and maintenance (Box 63, Folders 4-5)
  - RCA TR-600A NTSC television tape recorder volume1: catalog number MI-592501B, 1977 February (Box 64, Folders 1-2)
  - RCA TT-17FH, 25FH, 35FH, and 50FH VHF TV transmitters addendum volume 1 schematics and parts list, 1975 April (Box 64, Folders 3-4)
  - RCA TT-17FH, 25FH, 35FH, and 50FH VHF TV transmitters addendum volume 2 schematics and parts list, 1975 April (Box 64, Folders 5-6)
  - RCA TT-35FH/50FH VHF TV transmitter, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Scientific Atlanta 461 WB exciter instruction, 1976 April (Box 65, Folders 4-5)
  - Scientific Atlanta B-Mac sales information kit, 1986 April (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Scientific Atlanta V4.5TH-K video earth station technical proposal, 1987 March (Box 65, Folders 6)
  - ShibaSoku Co. Ltd. 925C color noise meter instruction, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Shure W10BT, W20R, and WL83 wireless microphone operator, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Sigma electronics BBG-144 blackburst timing module instruciton, 1982-1983 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - SMPTE? or ANSI? preliminary serial interface format for control video intelligent controller, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Sony BKU-701 computer interface board service, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Sony BVR-55, 55P, and 55PM remote control unit operation and maintenance 1st edition, 1st revision (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Sony PCM-7030 digital audio recorder maintenance 1st edition, 7th revision, 1993 November (Box 66, Folders 6-7)
  - Sony technical bulletins, 1984 (Box 66, Folders 8-9)
  - Sony technical bulletins, 1985 (Box 67, Folders 1-2)
  - Sony technical bulletins, 1986 (Box 67, Folders 3-4)
  - Sony technical bulletins, 1987 (Box 68, Folders 1-3)
  - Sony technical bulletins, 1988 (Box 69, Folders 1-3)
  - Sony technical bulletins, 1989 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Sound technology 1710a distortion measurement system operation, principals of operation, and maintenance, 1977 February (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Sound workshop logex 8 recording/mixing console operation, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Straight wire audio inc. matrix line amplifier assembly, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Tadrian electronic industries continuous communication system attendant user, 1986 (Box 68)
  - Tektronix 146/R145 NTSC test signal generator instruction, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Tektronix 520A NTSC vectorscope instruction, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Tektronix 521A PAL vectorscope instruction, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Tektronix 528 modification insert, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Tektronix 1740 series waveform/vector monitors instruciton, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Tektronix 2711/2712 spectrum analyzer programmer, 1992 February (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Tektronix 2712 spectrum analyzer user and pocket reference, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Tektronix TSG3, TSG5, TSG6, and TSP1 test signal generators instructions, 1976-1979 (Box 71, Folders 1-2)
  - Tektronix miscelaneous brouchures, 1982-1989 (Box 79, Folders 2-3)
  - Texscan MSI flexicaster-spectragen2 operation, 1982 December (Box 71, Folders 3)
  - Thomson broadcast 5500A, 5550, and 5555 color correction system operating and maintenance, 1975 September (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Thomson broadcast 9000 digital noise reducer operating and maintenance, 1978 February (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Thomson broadcast TTV 7610S SECAM precision decoder (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Thomson broadcast TTV 7671 digital to analog and analog to digital convertor; catalog number B7671-101 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Texas Instruments programmable calculator 58/59 applied statistics, aviation, electrical engineering, master library, math/utilities, personal programming, and surveying, 1977 (Box 72)
  - Transwave vanderbilt 8000 series K-8073 tiny basic microcomputer users, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - United Technologies Essex Controls relays and contact catalog, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Vital Industries inc. MU-1 squeezoom configuration (Box 73, Folders 1-2)
  - Vital Industries inc. VIX-1142/4A1 video production switcher system assembly and operation (Box 73, Folders 4-6)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume C external modulation and frequency monitors, 1988-1989 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume D part 1 audio distribution equipment, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume D part 2 audio distribution equipment, 1992 (Box 75, Folders 3-4)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume E audio monitoring equiment, 1991-1992 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume F part 2 audio signal processors, 1989-1992 (Box 74, Folders 7-8)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume G audio signal processors, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume H intercom system, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume I intercom system, 1991 (Box 76, Folders 2-3)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume J automated audio test system, 1991 (Box 77, Folders 1-3)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume K part 1 PBX system, 1988-1992 (Box 78, Folders 1-2)
  - Voice of America Morocco standard and custom operating and maintenance technical volume K part 2 PBX system, 1988-1992 (Box 78, Folders 3-4)
  - Wegener communications 1601, 1602, and 1651 mainframe instruction, 1982-1984 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Wegener communications 2000 series data transmission system operation and maintenance, 1982-1984 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Series 4: Selected binders for manuals
  - 12 representative binders from Ampex, Ikegami, Grass Valley Group, and others (Box 81)